At about 2000 local time (1900 UTC), a keeper was able to control the animal and load her onto a truck to take her to Winterthur, where the other circus animals were.
There were no reports of any damage or injuries during the incident, and although police held back onlookers, at least one bystander managed to capture video of the event.
The circus said that Sabu may have escaped after being frightened by storms near Zurich.
"After returning to the circus, she was said to be tired, but ""pleased to be back."""
Welsh poet Dannie Abse (81) and his wife Joan (78) were involved in a car crash while driving from Golders Green to their holiday home in Ogmore-by-Sea, South Wales.
"Mrs. Abse died instantly; Mr Abse suffered a broken rib."
The couple was returning from a poetry reading that they both had given.
Dannie Abse is an esteemed Jewish writer who lives in Glamorgan, South Wales.
Joan Abse, his wife, was an art historian and writer.
Dannie Abse is well-known for being a poet and a medical doctor.
Abse, in fact, was a specialist at a chest clinic for over thirty years.
But Abse is best known for his writings and has received numerous literary awards and fellowships.
In 1989, he received an honorary doctorate from the Universities of Wales.
The couple worked together editing two books in the 1980s.
Joan Abse leaves behind her husband, a son, and two daughters.
Palestinian extremist group Hamas has been invited to meet with representatives of the South African government.
Hamas won the Palestinian legislative council elections of January 2006 by a landslide and is now faced with forming a government and strained ties to European Union and the United States, which classify it as a terrorist organization responsible for several suicide attacks.
The South African deputy foreign minister Aziz Pahad confirmed on Thursday that the country is preparing a meeting with the controversial group.
According to Pahad South Africa wishes to share its experiences on the transformation from the Apartheid-era to democracy with the Palestinians and Israel.
South Africa also sees it important to keep in contact with Hamas in the search for peace in the Middle East.
Sami Abu Zuhri, a Hamas spookesman said that there is no date for talks with South Africa yet.
Russia has invited leaders of the Hamas for talks, which will begin on Friday.
The Russian invitation was the first one after the elections of January 2006.
However, Russia has put Hamas under pressure to recognize Israel and renounce violence.
There have been talks between Hamas leaders and the Turkish foreign minister, Abdullah Gul.
"Israeli foreign ministry spokesman voiced his ministry's concerns that ""giving legitimacy to an unreformed Hamas"" could turn the movement ""from a terrorist organization to a political party""."
Gary Bettman, the NHL commissioner, today announced that the 2004/2005 season of the National Hockey League has been canceled.
The announcement served only as official comfirmation of what was generally expected as wild speculation had raged during the past few days.
The dispute centered around player pay caps, which where staunchly opposed by the players.
The majority of NHL clubs have lost money over the last five years and as a result the clubs wanted to cap pay at a set amount.
The club owners would not go above $42.5 million for any one club, whilst the players refused to go below $49 million.
"Speaking about the cancellation, Gary Bettman said ""The shame of this is that our fans deserve better."""
This will be the first year since 1919 that the Stanley Cup - the top prize in the NHL - will not be awarded.
That year, a flu epidemic forced the finals to be called off.
Michael Jackson's This Is It, a documentary film based on world-famous singer Michael Jackson rehearsing for his last tour before his untimely death, will be premiered in at least 15 cinemas in cities all over the world simultaneously.
The film is due to premiere on October 27 and October 28.
The world cities may be in different time zones with different dates but they will all be premiering the film at exactly the same time.
One such premiere location is Los Angeles, in the US state of California, which will have the film starting at 1800 PT.
Another simultaneity is the Odeon Leicester Square cinema in London, England, which will start at 0100 GMT on October 27.
Other locations holding concurrent premieres are the South African city of Johannesburg, New York City in New York, German capital Berlin, Russian capital city Moscow, Japanese capital Tokyo, Australian city Sydney, French capital Paris, South Korean city Seoul, and Rio de Janeiro, a large city in Brazil.
Michael Jackson died on June 25, 2009 aged 50, after suffering from a cardiac arrest.
The movie will feature some of the rehearsal footage made in the weeks before his death.
In total, there will be at least 25 cinemas premiering the film, but not all of them will be released simultaneously.
Sony Pictures, the film production company, have yet to announce the other cities involved.
Tickets for the film will be available to purchase from Sunday, September 27.
The film is directed by Kenny Ortega, who previously directed all the High School Musical films.
He also directed some significant Michael Jackson events, such as his This Is It concert and Jackson's memorial service.
"Jeff Blake, chairman of worldwide marketing and distribution for Sony Pictures, said: ""Michael Jackson has an army of fans everywhere around the world... we are giving the audiences an incredible opportunity to join together in celebration of Michael Jackson's incredible career."""
Zimbabwe tied the second Group D match in the World Cup against Ireland at Sabina Park, Kingston, Jamaica.
Four male members of the paparazzi were arrested and charged on Wednesday with reckless driving in Mission Hills, California after following Britney Spears back to her mansion.
At least four others were also stopped by police, but were not arrested.
According to reports, police witnessed the entire incident saying that a fleet of paparazzi were following Spears at a high rate of speed around 11:20 p.m. PST (UTC-8).
They also say they followed her too closely and made unsafe lane changes in order to follow her.
Police also say that at least one of cars following Spears, who was driving her car, tried to run her off the road, but she was not able to identify the vehicle or the occupants.
They are reported to have verified her identity, and released her.
TMZ.com reports that police were checking to see if her license was valid, and was surprised that it was.
Spears was not charged with anything and despite the paparazzis' recklessness, Spears did not want the men arrested.
Britney Spears was part of the group, but was not driving recklessly, said spokeswoman for the Los Angeles Police Department, Sara Faden.
The IPC Alpine World Championships wrapped up yesterday in La Molina, Spain with a friendly, non-medal counting team event won by Austria.
The winner was tabulated based on the fastest score for a visually impaired skier on the team, a female skier on the team, and a male skier on the team.
The Austrian team included Markus Salcher, Roman Rabl, and Claudia Loesch for times counted, with Philipp Bonadimann, Thomas Grochar, and Martin Wuerz also competing.
The team event included ten teams representing eight countries, with the United States and Canada having two teams each and 54 skiers competing.
The United States team 1 came in second with Tyler Walker, Mark Bathum, and Alana Nichols times counting, and Heath Calhoun, Ralph Green, and Allison Jones also belonging to the team.
Russia came in third with Ivan Frantseva, Alexandr Alyabyev, and Mariya Papulova having their scores counted.
Hosts Spain finished last with Jon Santacana, Óscar Espallargas, and Úrsula Pueyo having their times counting, and Gabriel Gorce and Nathalie Carpanedo also members of the Spanish team.
The next major competition ahead of the 2014 Winter Paralympics is the test event in Sochi, Russia in March of this year.
A family of four adults and one minor has been reported dead after the house they were inhabiting in the city of Pichilemu, in Chile was allegedly intentionally set on fire on Sunday morning.
It's a great tragedy for the Pichileminian and couldn't pass unnoticed.
The police haven't been able to contact their respective relatives.
Dozens of people gathered outside the burnt house during Sunday afternoon.
It is believed that the fire affected at least five other homes.
New Zealand, Australia and England started their 2007 Rugby World Cup campaigns today with victories over Italy, Japan and the United States respectively.
Australia and tournament favorites New Zealand comprehensively defeated their opposition, while defending champions England produced a comparatively unimpressive display to overcome the American team.
Tournament favourites New Zealand dominated their opening match against Italy.
Richie McCaw opened the scoring after just 64 seconds and scored again in the seventh minutes.
Tries from Doug Howlett, Mils Muliaina and two from Sitiveni Sivivatu increased the All Black's imposing lead.
Just before half time, Marko Stanojevic scored a try for Italy taking the score to 43-7.
After the interval New Zealand scored five more tries, two each from Howlett and Jerry Collins and one from Chris Jack, with All Blacks fly half Daniel Carter kicking seventeen points during the match.
In the 71st minute, Mirco Bergamasco scored a consolation try for Italy.
Australia scored thirteen tries against Japan in their opening match.
A try from Nathan Sharpe and a hat-trick from Rocky Elsom put the Wallabies ahead by 23-3 at half time.
Australia overwhelmed Japan in the second half, scoring nine tries without reply.
Chris Latham, Berrick Barnes and Drew Mitchell claimed two tries each, and Adam Ashley-Cooper, George Smith and Adam Frier completed Australia's victory.
Japan's only points came from a Kōsei Ono penalty just before half time, while Stirling Mortlock kicked 27 points for Australia.
In contrast to the day's earlier matches, the England team overcame the United States by only eighteen points.
After 31 minutes the score was 9-3 with all points coming from penalties.
However Jason Robinson and Olly Barkley scored tries late in the first half for England, with the score 21-3 at half time.
Nine minutes after the interval Tom Rees scored England's third try, but they were not able to score again.
Matekitonga Moeakiola scored for the Americans in the 74th minute.
Hans and Josie Schaffer of Bedford, United Kingdom are possibly world record holders, now that they have a total of 99 grandchildren and great-grandchildren.
The pensioners spend most of the year saving for Christmas gifts.
Their eleven children have brought them 56 grandchildren and 43 great-grandchildren.
The kids just kept coming – and then their kids just kept coming, said Josie, 77, to the Sun newspaper.
Husband Hans was a prisoner of war in World War II, and went to work as a farmer for Josie's family.
While there is no existing record with Guinness for alive couples with the most grandchildren, Guinness World Records authorities say the couple very well might hold the record.
Glasgow resident Margaret McMillan had 123 grandchildren, but died last year at 98.
It wasn't until her funeral that the number, which included 15 great-great-grandchildren, was established by the family.
Governor Jon Corzine announced a bill that would provide $270 million to stem cell research.
"He announced, ""I don't want New Jersey to join the crowd of stem cell research states, I want New Jersey to lead it."""
BusinessWeek reports that the announcement came two days after Corzine announced that the state will give out $10 million in research grants next year, including $7 million for stem cell research.
A 15-year-old boy who allegedly stole a Melbourne, Australia tram and drove for 40 minutes picking up and setting down passengers, may yet be allowed to work as a tram driver, despite his nine charges related to the incident.
We have a very good recruiting policy and anybody who passes the muster for our recruiting policy we'd be glad to offer a job to, provided he's old enough to hold a driver's license, Yarra Trams Deputy Chief Executive, Dennis Cliche, told Australian Associated Press on Monday.
"Detective Senior Constable Barry Hills of Victoria Police, said of the boy, ""He's a nice lad, he's a good lad."""
I think his obsession just got the better of him.
Described as wearing a jacket similar to official Yarra Trams uniforms, the boy was caught on Sunday night by police in east suburban Kew, 15km from where the tram was stolen, when electricity was shut off to the route.
He is also accused of stealing a tram on Friday night, from South Melbourne depot.
