Nine minutes after the interval Tom Rees scored England's third try, but they were not able to score again.
Matekitonga Moeakiola scored for the Americans in the 74th minute.
Hans and Josie Schaffer of Bedford, United Kingdom are possibly world record holders, now that they have a total of 99 grandchildren and great-grandchildren.
The pensioners spend most of the year saving for Christmas gifts.
Their eleven children have brought them 56 grandchildren and 43 great-grandchildren.
The kids just kept coming – and then their kids just kept coming, said Josie, 77, to the Sun newspaper.
Husband Hans was a prisoner of war in World War II, and went to work as a farmer for Josie's family.
While there is no existing record with Guinness for alive couples with the most grandchildren, Guinness World Records authorities say the couple very well might hold the record.
Glasgow resident Margaret McMillan had 123 grandchildren, but died last year at 98.
It wasn't until her funeral that the number, which included 15 great-great-grandchildren, was established by the family.