Richie McCaw opened the scoring after just 64 seconds and scored again in the seventh minutes.
Tries from Doug Howlett, Mils Muliaina and two from Sitiveni Sivivatu increased the All Black's imposing lead.
Just before half time, Marko Stanojevic scored a try for Italy taking the score to 43-7.
After the interval New Zealand scored five more tries, two each from Howlett and Jerry Collins and one from Chris Jack, with All Blacks fly half Daniel Carter kicking seventeen points during the match.
In the 71st minute, Mirco Bergamasco scored a consolation try for Italy.